Guide to the Trinity College of Arts and Sciences, Office of the Dean records, 1911-2006 UA.25.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Container List
  - Standing Committees of UFC, 1964-1969 (Box 15)
  - Undergraduate Research Assistantship Program, 1969-1970 (Box 15)
  - United Fund Drive: Deans, 1969 (Box 15)
  - University Facilities, 1970 (Box 16)
  - University Policy and Planning Advisory Committee, 1967 (Box 16)
  - Washington Summer Intern Program, 1970 (Box 16)
  - West Campus Living-Learning Corridors, 1970 (Box 16)
  - WCCC, 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Woman's College: Board of Visitors, 1971 (Box 16)
  - Dean's Office: Miscellaneous, 1952-1969 (Box 16)
  - Academic Council, 1969-1970 (Box 16)
  - Admissions: Undergraduate, 1969-1972 (Box 16)
  - Admissions Office, Reports from, 1969-1972 (Box 16)
  - Admissions and Financial Aid: Budgetary, 1969-1970 (Box 16)
  - Alumni Office, Letters from re: T.C., 1957-1968 (Box 16)
  - AAUP: National Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 16)
  - Appeals Board, Faculty, 1966 (Box 16)
  - Association of American Colleges Bulletins, 1969 (Box 16)
  - AAU, 1970 (Box 16)
  - Association of Independent Houses, 1967-1968 (Box 16)
  - AIH Meetings, 1969 (Box 16)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference, 1969 (Box 16)
  - Deferred Tuition Plan, 1971 (Box 16)
  - Distinguished Professor Seminar: Professor Paul M. Gross, 1965 (Box 16)
  - Distinguished Professor Seminar: Professor Bruce Wardropper, 1965 (Box 16)
  - Distinguished Professor Seminar: Professor Ray C. Petry, 1966 (Box 16)
  - Distinguished Professor Seminar: Professor Iain Hamilton, 1965 (Box 16)
  - Distinguished Professor Seminars, 1964-1966 (Box 16)
  - Drugs, Illicit Use of CONFIDENTIAL, 1967-1970 (Box 16)
  - Committee on Educational Administration, 1969-1971 (Box 16)
  - Educational Administration Advisory Group, 1970-1972 (Box 16)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 16)
  - Enrollments, Admission Projections, 1967-1968 (Box 16)
  - President's Report, 1957-1968 (Box 16)
  - Guide Material: Forms, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Guide Material: Personnel Cards, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Guide Material: Social Functions, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Guide Material: Guide Material: Lists to be Made, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Guide Material: Housing Information, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Guide Material: Fraternities, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Guide Material: Activities, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Office of the Dean of Men: Work Plan, 1955-1964 (Box 16)
  - Samples: Material Used by Office of Dean of Men, 1963 (Box 16)
  - Work Reports, 1948-1956 (Box 16)
  - Trinity College Miscellaneous, 1946-1947 (Box 17)
  - Work Report, 1957-1965 (Box 17)
  - Yearly Report: Office of the Dean of Men, 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - Academe, 1971-1972 (Box 17)
  - Academic-Forestry, Academic-Law Combinations, 1968 (Box 17)
  - Academic Freedom Students, 1964-1968 (Box 17)
  - Academic Standards, Committee on, 1968-1970 (Box 17)
  - Committee on Academic Standards: Minutes of the Meeting, 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Administrative Committee on Development, 1970-1971 (Box 17)
  - Administrative Council, 1969-1972 (Box 17)
  - Administrative Interns, Committee on, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Advisory Group to the Dean of Faculty, 1969-1971 (Box 17)
  - Affirmative Action Plan, 1970-1972 (Box 17)
  - Afro-American Society, 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Afro-American Society: Studies Program, etc., 1969-1970 (Box 17)
  - Air Force: ROTC, 1968-1972 (Box 17)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1969-1972 (Box 17)
  - Alumni Committees: Admissions, 1970-1971 (Box 17)
  - Duke Alumni Meeting: SENC Duke Alumni Association, 1971 (Box 17)
  - American Civil Liberties Union: Academic Freedom and Civil Liberties of Students, 1970 (Box 17)
  - American University Exchange Program, 1971-1972 (Box 17)
  - American Medical Association: AMA Update, 1971-1972 (Box 17)
  - American Council on Education, Meeting, 1969-1972 (Box 17)
  - Angier B. Duke Memorial Scholarship Program, 1969-1971 (Box 17)
  - Annual Press Association Dinner, 1970 (Box 17)
  - Application for Positions: Undergraduate Admr., 1970 (Box 17)
  - ASDU: Student Prospective, 1970 (Box 17)
  - ASDU: Resolutions, 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - ASDU: President, 1968-1974 (Box 17)
  - ASDU: The Association, 1967 (Box 17)
  - ASDU: Legislation, 1970-1971 (Box 17)
  - Association of African Students, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - Aspen Black Studies Conference, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Association of College and University Housing Officers, Newsletter, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Assistantship, Bursary Program: Undergraduates, 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Association of American Universities, 1970-1972 (Box 18)
  - Association of Independent Houses, 1967-1969 (Box 18)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Biological Sciences Council, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Beaufort Marine Laboratory, 1971 (Box 18)
  - Board of Education: United Methodist Church, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Black Studies, 1971-1973 (Box 18)
  - Blackburn's National Council Address, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Black Studies Program: Analysis, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Board System: Dining Halls, East Campus, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - B.S. in Health Sciences, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Brown University, 1965-1969 (Box 18)
  - Brown University, Student Conduct at "Community and Partnership", 1967 (Box 18)
  - Bubas, Victor A. Correspondence with, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
  - Bulletins of D.U.: Undergraduate Instruction, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - Business Consultant Guidance, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
  - Calendar-Modified, 1971 (Box 18)
  - Campus Community Council, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - Campus Recruitment, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Carnegie Quarterly, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
  - Chancellor's Memos - Unclassified, 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Charleston Duke Alumni Association, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Chemistry Department, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
  - Chronicle, The, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
  - Child Care Center, 1972 (Box 18)
  - College Board Review, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - College Dean's Group Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - College Level Examination, CEEB, 1969-1972 (Box 18)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1968-1970 (Box 18)
  - College Scholarship Service Assembly, 1966-1969 (Box 18)
  - Commonwealth Studies, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Computer Science, Dept. of, 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Comparative Literature, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - Community Colleges of North Carolina, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Conflicts: Committee on Origins and Resolutions of, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Conflict Resolution, P.S. 120 Problems of War and Peace, 1971 (Box 18)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Consultants, Fees, etc., 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - Consultants and Fees, Policy on, 1971 (Box 18)
  - Conferences - Representation, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Conference Attendance Record, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Office of Continuing Education, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - Continuing Education, The Woman's College, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Course Load Reduction-Tuition Remission SS-for certain student leaders, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Counseling Center, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - Costing Higher Education, Problems in, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Curriculum, The New Undergraduate Conferences and literature distributed, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Dateline, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Deans of Women, NC Association Annual Meeting, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Deferred Tuition Plan, 1971 (Box 18)
  - Department Chairmen, Some notices to, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Departmental Major Requirements, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
  - Development Office, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Distinguished Professor Seminars, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Drinking Regulations: Discussions, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Dormitory Closure-Pegram Protest, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Drug Policy, DU, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Duke-NCCU Joint Committee Meetings, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Edgemont-Living and Learning, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Education Abstracts, 1969-1972 (Box 18)
  - Educational Administration Advisory Group, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
  - Education Administration, Committee on, 1968-1972 (Box 18)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Enrollments, Entering, 1971 (Box 18)
  - Enrollment Projections, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Engineering, Minutes of School of, Faculty Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - Engineering, School of, 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Executive Committee Agenda, Board of Trustees, 1969-1972 RESTRICTED (Box 18)
  - Examinations, Final, 1970 (Box 18)
  - External Degree Plans, Office of CEEB/ETS, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - Faculties of Arts and Sciences, Summary Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Faculty Census Forms, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - Financial Aid, Angier B. Duke Memorial, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous, 1969-1975 (Box 18)
  - Freshmen Advisors: Lists and Letters, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Freshmen Advising, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - Housing, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Hospital Administration Enrichment Program, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Mailings, 1969-1971 (Box 19)
  - Notre Dame, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Nursing, School of, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Transfers-School of Nursing, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Officer Education Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - Omega House, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Paramedical Programs, Duke Medical Center, 1969-1970 (Box 19)
  - Pass-Fail Option, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Pennsylvania Higher Education Assistance Agency, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Physical Education, 1969-1972 (Box 19)
  - Physical Education Requirement, 1971 (Box 19)
  - Policies, Procedures, Scope Rules, etc., 1973-1974 (Box 19)
  - Policy Science, Institute of, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Post-Graduate Plans, 1966-1969 (Box 19)
  - Pre-Law Advising, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Pre-registration and Faculty Advising, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Provost Group, 1969-1972 (Box 19)
  - Publications Group, 1970-1971 (Box 19)
  - Public Education and Training of Teachers, Committee on, 1969-1971 (Box 19)
  - Putney Reading Services, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 19)
  - Privacy, Student-Discussions, 1969-1970 (Box 19)
  - Privacy Policy and Regulations, 1969-1970 (Box 19)
  - Provost Group, 1969-1972 (Box 19)
  - Professors Emeriti, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Residential Life Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 19)
  - Refund Policy re: Student Withdrawals, 1969-1970 (Box 19)
  - Refrigerators in Dorms, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Residential life Evaluation Committee, 1971 (Box 19)
  - Request from other Institutions, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Regional Spotlight-SREB, 1969-1972 (Box 19)
  - Regional Education Laboratory, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Research Council, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Retention-Attrition Reports, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Residences: Room contract and agreements, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Research Foundation, George C. Marshall, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Research Projects and Undergraduate Residences, 1969-1970 (Box 19)
  - ROTC Issues, 1969-1972 (Box 19)
  - Study of Staff and Section Needs, New Curriculum, 1967-1968 (Box 20)
  - Study Abroad, 1970 (Box 20)
  - Student Records, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Student Union, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Student Union, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Student Union, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Student Health Advisory Committee and Brochure, 1971-1972 (Box 20)
  - State Board of Higher Education, 1971-1972 (Box 20)
  - Scholarships, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Angier B. Duke Fellowships, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Association of Naval ROTC Colleges Biennial Meeting, 1968 (Box 20)
  - SCOPE, 1969 (Box 20)
  - SFAC, 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Statement of Intent-Grant Applications, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Statesmen in Medicine-Woodhall, 1971 (Box 20)
  - State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, National Assoc., 1971 (Box 20)
  - Student Assistantship Program-Bursary, 1969-1970 (Box 20)
  - Student Mental Health, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Student Health Advisory Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 20)
  - Teacher-Course Evaluation, 1970-1972 (Box 20)
  - Student Housing Committee, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Teacher Education-Duke, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Teaching, Undergraduate, Improvement of, 1964 (Box 20)
  - Trinity College Staff Meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - Tuition Subsidies, Course Load Reduction for Certain Student Leaders-Agreement, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Undergraduate Housing, 1970 (Box 20)
  - University Calendar, 1970 (Box 20)
  - University Research Council, 1969 (Box 20)
  - University Convocation, 1969 (Box 20)
  - University Presidents' Conference-Boston, 1970 (Box 20)
  - University Review Committee, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Visitation Policy Proposal, 1972 (Box 20)
  - UNC-CH Dean Dawson-Conversation Reports, 1969 (Box 20)
  - University Union, 1971 (Box 20)
  - University Schedule Committee, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Vice Provost's Staff Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 20)
  - Welch Harriss Scholarships, 1972 (Box 20)
  - Board of Visitors of the Woman's College, Duke University, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Work Study Program, 1970 (Box 20)
  - Woman's College Internship Program, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966-1972 (Box 20)
  - Program II, 1972-1977 (Box 20)
  - Opportunity Courses, 1972-1977 (Box 20)
  - A Report on the Institute for Undergraduate Curricular Reform, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Study Abroad, 1964-1979 (Box 21)
  - Women's Network, 1979-1971 (Box 21)
  - Visiting Scholars: Latin America, 1965-1968 (Box 21)
  - Academic Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 21)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, Board of Trustees, 1972-1974 RESTRICTED (Box 21)
  - Academic Calendars, 1965-1973 (Box 21)
  - Accreditation Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 21)
  - Ad Hoc Committee, Privately Financed Off-Campus Housing, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Administrative Internship Program, 1972-1973 (Box 21)
  - Administrative Reorganization, 1968-1972 (Box 21)
  - Admissions and Financial Aid, 1972-1974 (Box 21)
  - Minority Recruiting, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Admissions: Freshman Bulletins, 1967-1974 (Box 21)
  - Admissions: Experimental Program, 1967-1970 RESTRICTED (Box 21)
  - Admissions: January Freshmen, 1971-1973 (Box 21)
  - Admissions Packet, 1967-1972 (Box 21)
  - Advanced Placement Program, 1972-1973 (Box 21)
  - Advising Information Directory, AIPD, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Affirmative Action, 1972-1973 (Box 21)
  - Afro-American Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 21)
  - A. J. Fletcher Musical Awards, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1967-1972 (Box 21)
  - Alumni Admissions Advisory Committee, 1965-1974 (Box 21)
  - Alumni Affairs Department, 1968-1974 (Box 21)
  - Alumni Children at Duke, 1966-1971 (Box 21)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - American Assembly, 1967-1970 (Box 21)
  - American Association of Higher Education, 1972-1973 (Box 21)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1968-1974 (Box 21)
  - American Association of University Women, 1967-1973 (Box 21)
  - American Council on Education, 1966-197 (Box 21)
  - Anthropology Department, 1973-1974 (Box 22)
  - Appeals Board, 1966-1974 RESTRICTED (Box 22)
  - Art Department, 1967-1973 (Box 22)
  - Art Exhibits: East Duke Building, 1966-1969 (Box 22)
  - Arts and Crafts Workshop, 1968-1973 (Box 22)
  - Assistantship Program, 1970-1974 (Box 22)
  - ASDU, 1967-1973 (Box 22)
  - Association of African Students, 1970-1973 (Box 22)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1966-1973 (Box 22)
  - Association of American Universities, 1953-1970 (Box 22)
  - Baldwin Federation, 1972-1974 (Box 22)
  - Robert Spencer Bell Student Aid Fund, 1974 (Box 22)
  - Mary Duke Biddle Foundation, 1971-1973 (Box 22)
  - William Blackburn Scholarship, 1973 (Box 22)
  - Botany Department, 1968-1971 (Box 22)
  - Braxton-Craven Scholarship, 1973 (Box 22)
  - Roberta Florence Brinkley International Scholarship Fund, 1963-1974 (Box 22)
  - Building and Grounds Committee, Committee of the University Trustees, 1968-1969 RESTRICTED (Box 22)
  - Bulletins: Undergraduates, 1964-1973 (Box 22)
  - Bureau of Public Information, 1967-1970 (Box 22)
  - School of Business Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 22)
  - Business Manager, 1966-1973 (Box 22)
  - Campus Community Council, 1969-1973 (Box 22)
  - Career and Continuing Education, 1969-1975 (Box 22)
  - Career and Community Service Internships, 1967-1974 (Box 22)
  - Center for Southern Studies, 1970 (Box 22)
  - University Chaplan, 1972 (Box 22)
  - Check Sheet, 1973-1974 (Box 22)
  - Chemistry Pilot Program, 1973 (Box 22)
  - Chronicle, 1966-1972 (Box 22)
  - Class Comparison, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Commencement, 1968-1974 (Box 22)
  - Comp. for Central Campus Facility, 1970-1973 (Box 23)
  - Committee on Comparative Literature, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Committee on International Studies, 1967-1971 (Box 23)
  - Committee on Learning Disorders, 1970 (Box 23)
  - Committee Organization and Duties, University, 1964 (Box 23)
  - Committee on the Use of University Facilities, 1964-1972 (Box 23)
  - Committee to Investigate Student Charges of Discrimination in Employment Practices, 1970 (Box 23)
  - Conferences, 1970-1974 (Box 23)
  - Course Load Reduction for Student Leaders, 1968-1974 (Box 23)
  - University Council, 1970-1971 (Box 23)
  - University Counseling Center, 1966-1974 (Box 23)
  - Creative and Performing Arts, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Curriculum Study, 1964-1973 (Box 23)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1967-1973 (Box 23)
  - Dean's Discretionary Fund, 1970-1974 (Box 23)
  - Deaths: Students, 1967-1973 (Box 23)
  - Department Chairmanship, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - Department Reviews, 1970-1973 (Box 23)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Dining Halls, 1968-1974 (Box 23)
  - Dining Halls Board Plan, 1968-1971 (Box 23)
  - Divinity School, 1968-1973 (Box 23)
  - Dormitory Commons Rooms, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Dormitory Housing and License Agreement, 1971-1972 (Box 23)
  - Dormitory Open: Vacations, 1969-1973 (Box 23)
  - Dormitory Renovation and New Dormitory, 1969-1972 (Box 23)
  - Planning Committee for Drama, 1972-1974 (Box 23)
  - Drinking Regulations, 1967-1973 (Box 23)
  - Drugs, 1966-1971 (Box 23)
  - Duke Environmental Center, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Duke Summer Theatre, 1972-1974 (Box 23)
  - DUERAC, Duke University Employee Relations Advisory Council, 1968-1974 (Box 23)
  - Educational Administration Advisory Group, 1969-1972 (Box 23)
  - Educational Administration Committee, 1967-1971 (Box 23)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1967-1974 (Box 23)
  - Educational Facilities Committee Minutes, 1967-1974 (Box 23)
  - EFC: Community Health-Sciences Building, 1968 (Box 23)
  - EFC: Denominational Centers, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - EFC: Student Facility Health Center, 1966 (Box 23)
  - EFC: Information Center, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Education Department, 1971-1973 (Box 23)
  - Emeriti, 1967-1974 (Box 23)
  - Energy Conservation, 1973 (Box 23)
  - Engineering School, 1970-1974 (Box 23)
  - English Department, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Enrollment, 1967-1974 (Box 23)
  - ESSO Educational Foundation, 1966-1974 (Box 24)
  - Exchange Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
  - Faculty Advisors, 1964-1974 (Box 24)
  - Faculty Club, 1965-1970 (Box 24)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1967-1971 (Box 24)
  - Faculty: Miscellaneous Information, 1971-1973 (Box 24)
  - Few Federation, 1972-1974 (Box 24)
  - Federations, 1969-1973 (Box 24)
  - Ferrum College, 1973 (Box 24)
  - Financial Aid Reporting System, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Financing of Higher Education, 1968-1970 (Box 24)
  - Foreign Student Advisory Committee, 1962-1973 (Box 24)
  - Founders Day, 1967-1973 (Box 24)
  - Fraternities, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
  - Freshman Advisory Council, 1968-1973 (Box 24)
  - Friends of Duke University Library, 1963-1974 (Box 24)
  - Fulbright Grants, 1967-1973 (Box 24)
  - Fund Raising Programs, 1966-1971 (Box 24)
  - Gifts, 1962-1974 (Box 24)
  - Governance Commission Report, 1970-1973 (Box 24)
  - Graduate Center, 1967-1973 (Box 24)
  - Graduates: Instructions for Preparation of List, 1972-1974 (Box 24)
  - Graduate School File, 1964-1974 (Box 24)
  - Grants, 1963-1973 (Box 24)
  - Guest Suite: Wilson House, 1973 (Box 24)
  - J. Welch Harriss Scholarship, 1973 (Box 24)
  - House Counselors: Miscellaneous, 1967-1973 (Box 24)
  - House Courses, 1972-1974 (Box 24)
  - Housing, 1968-1974 (Box 24)
  - Housing Bureau, 1965-1974 (Box 24)
  - History: Panhellenic Housing, 1969-1973 (Box 24)
  - Humanities, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Human Sexuality Information and Counseling Center, 1974 (Box 24)
  - Ideas, 1968-1973 (Box 24)
  - Inauguration of President Sanford, 1970 (Box 24)
  - Information and Regulations Bulletin, 1966-1974 (Box 24)
  - Innovative Teaching Group, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Institute of Public Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 1971-1974 (Box 24)
  - Institutional Research, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Institutes, 1972-1974 (Box 25)
  - Insurance: Student Accident and Sickness Policy, 1969-1974 (Box 25)
  - Internal Development and Alumni Relations Council, 1969-1974 (Box 25)
  - International Student Scholarship Committee, 1956-1969 (Box 25)
  - Job Descriptions: Dean and Staff, 1969-1974 (Box 25)
  - Job Reclassification, 1969-1970 (Box 25)
  - Key-Card System, 1969-1970 (Box 25)
  - Kilgo Federation, 1971-1974 (Box 25)
  - Kuwait University Cooperative Program, 1973 (Box 25)
  - Laboratory School, 1973 (Box 25)
  - School of Law, 1967-1971 (Box 25)
  - Letter to Students, 1961-1973 (Box 25)
  - Library Information, 1966-1973 (Box 25)
  - Loyalty Fund Program, 1968-1974 (Box 25)
  - Louise Oliver Litaker Scholarship Fund, 1969-1974 (Box 25)
  - Majors: by Department, 1963-1973 (Box 25)
  - Mail Schedule, 1965-1973 (Box 25)
  - Marshall Scholarships, 1966-1972 (Box 25)
  - Marine Laboratory, 1974-1975 (Box 25)
  - Master Plan of Campus, 1969-1970 (Box 25)
  - Math Department, 1964-1974 (Box 25)
  - Media Center, 1972-1973 (Box 25)
  - Medical Center, 1966-1974 (Box 25)
  - Mental Health Service, 1967-1972 (Box 25)
  - Merger, 1970-1973 (Box 25)
  - Methodist Scholarship Offer, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence with Students, 1972-1974 (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box 25)
  - Music Building, 1963-1974 (Box 25)
  - Music Department, 1967-1974 (Box 25)
  - Medical Composition Prize, 1967-1974 (Box 25)
  - Naming of Buildings, 1969 (Box 25)
  - National Merit Scholarship Program, 1962-1973 (Box 25)
  - Naval ROTC, 1969-1973 (Box 25)
  - The Negro in Higher Education, 1964-1973 (Box 25)
  - NC Association of Academic Deans, 1967-1972 (Box 25)
  - School of Nursing, 1967-1974 (Box 25)
  - Office of Physical Planning, 1963-1972 (Box 25)
  - Office of Placement Services, 1966-1974 (Box 25)
  - Offices: Students, 1966-1972 (Box 25)
  - Office Supplies and Equipment, 1963-1970 (Box 25)
  - Old Chemistry Building, 1965-1970 (Box 25)
  - O.S.R.'s: Old Students Returning, 1967-1974 RESTRICTED (Box 25)
  - Operations and Maintenance, 1967-1971 (Box 25)
  - Orientation Week, 1967-1974 (Box 26)
  - Paging Services, 1974 (Box 26)
  - Parking, 1971-1974 (Box 26)
  - Part-Time Students, 1974 (Box 26)
  - Patent Policy, 1973 (Box 26)
  - Personnel Office, 1969-1974 RESTRICTED (Box 26)
  - Personnel: Non-Academic, 1962-1973 (Box 26)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1967-1974 (Box 26)
  - Physical Education, 1970-1971 (Box 26)
  - Department of Physical Education, 1973 (Box 26)
  - Physical Education Building and Needs, 1966-1974 (Box 26)
  - Physical Education Department for Men, 1968-1973 (Box 26)
  - Policy on Student Employment at Duke, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Population Studies Workshop, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Pre-Law Advising, 1972-1974 (Box 26)
  - Pre-Med Advising, 1972-1974 (Box 26)
  - President Sanford, 1969-1974 (Box 26)
  - Privacy of Students' Rooms, 1967-1970 (Box 26)
  - Property Officer, 1973 (Box 26)
  - Prospective Student Publications, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Provost Group, 1968-1974 (Box 26)
  - Publications Board, 1970 (Box 26)
  - Questionnaire Policy, 1964-1970 (Box 26)
  - Questionnaires, 1971-1973 (Box 26)
  - Records Problems, 1963-1973 (Box 26)
  - Registrar, 1967-1974 (Box 26)
  - Registration Procedures, 1967-1971 (Box 26)
  - Relocation of Offices, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - Reorganization: Trinity College of Arts and Sciences, 1971-1974 (Box 26)
  - Research Council, 1968-1974 (Box 26)
  - Residence Requirements for Duke Degree, 1968-1971 (Box 26)
  - Residential Governance Study Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 26)
  - Residential Judicial System, 1973 (Box 26)
  - Residential Life Evaluation Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 26)
  - Rhodes Scholarships, 1972-1974 RESTRICTED (Box 27)
  - Russell Sage Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 27)